all right we found a bigger problem and
I'm just going to show it because it's
going to be very smart I I think this is
one of the main reasons that I don't
like
Elm um is that this can exist so
postgress version 13 there's a
dependency not only here but also in the
default value spot which I've talked
about in another video on postgress
version 13 that's app version 13 the
postest version
13.16
okay
and
um yeah it says here image 13
right so and and again the values file
is hardcoded to the Tagg version of post
version of post and maybe I'm missing
something so I'm making a video about
this yet down here we see that the
repository dependency this is this is
this is how Helm does sub charts
um which I'm not very strong in but this
right here says that there is a subchart
dependency on version 15 x.x of the
chart of the postgress chart the bitnami
chart for
postgress right and and if we go to um
we use the tool I just wrote um to list
all the charts for a given version of an
app app version we can see that the
charts the chart versions for version
16.4 of the postrest
app start at 15.5 so 15.5 is the first
chart so what we can derive from that I
think is that there is a hardcoded
subchart
dependency on the chart of 15 which is a
dependency on postgress version app
version
16.4 or
higher and yet the image here is
13.16 I don't know I don't know what's
going on there but if indeed it is using
so the good news here is if indeed this
is pulling in one of the charts from 15
Point whatever we might actually end up
getting automated backups through a
regular Cron job which can be configured
through the values. yaml file that I
found in the most recent recent version
of post grass's chart benami
postgress but that was not in the harbor
yaml file Val out file which we already
know is totally screwed up because it's
got It's pegged it's pegged to 13
because of an old um uh super old
dependency so what I'm trying to say is
the harbor values file is totally
screwed up it's totally screwed up and
there's a very strong possibility that
it's missing in several key areas that
would have come in from the dependencies
chart including the activation of
backups by changing one value from false
to
true instead of writing your an entire
postgress backup solution and attacking
on your own Cron job and your own
customized you know customizations at
amop which we've done in the past we've
spent a lot of time it's already written
it's all there it's all already in the
postc cross chart but you just can't see
it because you're just looking at the
anals file the values file for Harbor
which doesn't include all the values
that are potentially there for post I
could very well be getting something
wrong here but I'm just going to put
this out there because if you know the
answer to this you want to put a comment
in there please do this is making me
absolutely despise Helm even more
because the fact that this even exists
right now if if I'm right about this
then this is a this this values file
this this harm this Helm chart did I say
harm
it literally allows
people it it's it's
completely broken it's completely broken
because it says you have to use the
chart
15x you know but then it also forces the
dependency on postgress
13 but 15. X of the chart is is version
16.4 it's totally broken that's all bye